Guide to the Edward M. Bassett papers, 1892-1948
Bassett, Edward M. papers, 1892-1948
- Outgoing correspondence
  - Farrell, Thomas J., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Farrell, William V., 1911-1915 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Faunce, Miss Annie C., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Fearn, Charles C., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Feinman, Mrs. Sarah, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Fell, U.M., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Felt and Tarrant Manufacturing Co., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Ferretti, Antonio, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Fettis, William G., 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Fifth Avenue Bank, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Findley, Everett T., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Finlay, Quitman, Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Fischer, J.J., 1914 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Fishel and Oliver, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 177a)
  - Fisher, Edmund D., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Fisher, Edmund D., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Fitton, Mr. Arthur and Mrs. Elizabeth, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Fitzgerald, Mrs. Catherine S., 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Fitzgerald, D.J., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Flatbrush Congregational Church, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Flatbrush Gas Company, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Flatbrush Trust Co., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 184a)
  - Fleit, Harry, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Foley, James C., Esq., Foley and Powell, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Ford, George B., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Fortenbach, H., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Fosdick, Raymond B., Esq., 1924 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Fox, Mrs. Mary C., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Fraser, William A., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Friebolin and Byers, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Friestedt, L.P., 1912 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Friestedt, L.P., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Fuller, Hon. Charles H., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Fuller, Hon. Charles H., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Furber, William C., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - General F Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - General F Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - General F Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - General F Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - General F Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - General F Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - General F Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - General F Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - General F Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - General F Correspondence, 1922-1927 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - General F Correspondence, 1912-1923 (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - Ganse, Clinton D., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Garretson, Miss Ada M., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Garretson, Mitchell P., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Garvey, Isaac E., 1922 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Garwood, S., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Gaynor, Hon. William J., 1911-1913 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Geis, Hohn F., Secretary, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - German Savings Bank, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gernannt, Mrs. Emma, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Gibson, Mrs. Amy L., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Gibson, George H., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Gilbert, Alexander, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Gilbert, Alexander, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gillespie, Earl A., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Gilpatric, F. Raymond, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gilpatric, G. Harold, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Gilpatric, C.W., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Gilpatric, Walter H., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Gilpatric, Walter H., Esq., 1922-1924 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Glenn, Mrs. Clara H., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Glenn, Mrs. Clara H., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Gload, Frank F., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Goetz, George Z., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Goetzinger, M.E., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Goodman, Mrs. Ruth, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Goodwin, Dr. E.J., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Goodwin, Dr. E.J., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Goodyear, Prof. William H., 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Goodyear, Prof. William H, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Gorman, Jones M., Esq., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Granite Securities Corporation, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Graves, Louis, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Gray, Dr. John H., 1912-1914 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Gray, Lou, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Green, E.F., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Greene, Everett, Esq., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Greene, Hon. John, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Greenough, Mrs. Adelade, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Gregg, Mrs. Ada, 1923-1925 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Gremmels, Charles E., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Gries, John M., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Griffith, Frederick W., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Griffith Investing Company, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Grout, Edward M., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Groves, J.M. Realty Co., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Guaranty Trust Co., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Gueritey, Charles H., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Gunder, Howard H., 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Gunnison, Frederick E., 1912-1914 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Gunnison, Herbert F., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Gunnison, Dr. W.B., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - General G Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - General G Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - General G Correspondence, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - General G Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - General G Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - General G Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - General G Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - General G Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - General G Correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - General G Correspondence, 1922-1924 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - General G Correspondence, 1922-1924 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - General G Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - General G Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - General G Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Hafely, Alfred C., 1912 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Hafely, Alfred C., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Hafely, Alfred C., 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Hafely, Mrs. Caroline L., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Hafely, Gerard D., 1922-1924 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Hafely, Miss Lillian M.L., 1922-126 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Half, Arthur C., 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Half, Arthur C., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Haines, Charles W. Esq., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Hall, Frank A. and Sons, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Hall, John W., 1924 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Haller, Professor William, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Hammesfahr, Miss Katherine, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Hammesfahr, Miss Katherine, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Hancock, W.J., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Hanson, Bert, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Harkness, Leroy T., Esq., 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Harkness, Leroy T., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Harkness, Leroy T., 1916-1924 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Harley, Mrs. Sarah S., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Harper and Bros., 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Harper and Bros., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Harrington and Davidson, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Harrington, Mr. and Mrs. Charles M., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Harrington, Mr. and Mrs. Charles M., 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Harrington, Mrs. Mary B., 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Harris, Charles, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Harris, Dodds and Kegy, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Harris, Mrs. Irene, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Harter, Eugene W., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Harter, Eugene W., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Hartung, Edward, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Hatheway, Curtis R., Esq., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Hawley, Alfred J., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Hawley, Amos P., 1923-1925 (Box 3, Folder 99a)
  - Hayden, Thomas E., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Hayes, Dennis, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Hays, Miss Mary, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Heath and Norris, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Hegemann, Dr. Werner, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Hellmich, Mrs. Mary D., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Hempling, Mrs. Gussie, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Hendrick, Mrs. Linda W., 1912-1915 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Hendrick, Mrs. Linda W., 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Hendrick, Welland, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Hendrick, Welland, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Herb, Miss Elizabeth, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Herlihy, Miss E.M., 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Herrick, Abraham J., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Herrick, Vette and Peregrine, 1924-1925 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Herriman, Samuel C., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Herring, Rev. Hubert, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Hewins, Mrs. Mary L., 1922 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Hewins, S.W., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Hewins, S.W., 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Higgins, Dr. Joseph A., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Hilgers, Mrs. Jeanette, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Hirschman, Stuard, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Hoffman, William, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Hogan, Walter V., 1924-1925 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Holt, Thomas, S., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Home Crest Co., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Home Talk Publishing Co., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Home Title Insurance Co., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Homewood Holding Co., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Hooker, George E., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Hooper, Dr. Franklin W., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Horeneburg, Henry, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Hornstein, Leon, Esq., 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - House, Grossman and Vorhaus, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Howe, Dr. Frederick C., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Howes, A.W., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Hoyt, Mrs. Emma L., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Hoyt, Mrs. Emma L., 1923-1926 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Hughes, Hon. Charles L., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Hughes, Hon. Charles L., 1917-1924 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Huges, C.V. Oden, Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Hull, E.F., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Hurley, William P., 1922-1923 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - General H Correspondence, 1892-1912 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - General H Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - General H Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - General H Correspondence, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - General H Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Ideal Ventilator Co., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Ihlder, John, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Ingersoll, Hon. Raymond V., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Irving Bank Columbia Trust Company, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - General I Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Jaburg, Henry K., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Jacobs, Elmer R., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Jefferies, Charles E., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Jemison, S.S., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Johnson and Levy, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Johnson, James P., 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Johnson, Myles, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Johnston, William P., 1924 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Jones, Miss Edith T., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Jones, Edward N., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Jones, Edward N., 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Jordan, Mrs. Daisy E., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Judd, B.A. Esq., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - General J Correspondence, 1911-1915 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - General J Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - General J Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - General J Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Kaltenborn, Mr. and Mrs. Hans V., 1919-1937 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Kase, Miss Virginia A., 1922-125 (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Kaufman, Miss Lydia E., 1923-1926 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Keating, Robert W., 1925 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Kells, W.J. Manufacturing Co., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Kelly, Samuel E., 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Kelsey, Mrs. Anna M., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Kelsey, C.E., 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Kelsey, C.E, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Kemmann, G., 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Kemmann, G., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Kendall, Mrs. E.F., 1922-1925 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Kendall, Henry P., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Kenney, John J., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Kerr, William D., 1913 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Khorge, Mrs. Mary A., 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Kilborn, Rev. John L., D.D., 1925-1924 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Kilgallon, James, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Kimball, V.B., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Kimball, W.W. Co., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - King, Horatio C., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - King, H.G., 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - King, J. Travis, Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Kings County Lighting Company, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Kirk, William A., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Kistler, Fred B., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Klag, John C., 1922-1924 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Klinck, Jacob C., 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Klueg, Mrs. Bertha, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Knickerbocker Field Club, 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Knickerbocker Field Club, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Koester, Frank, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Korostishevsky, Mrs. Beckie, 1923-1925 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Kossack, Mrs. Jennie, 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Kowalski, Kon, 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Kowalski, Kon, 1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - General K Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - General K Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - General K Correspondence, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - General K Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - General K Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - General K Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - General K Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - General K Correspondence, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - General K Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - General K Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - General K Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - General K Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - General K Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Lachapelle, Mrs. Malvina, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ladd, Arthur W., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lane, Messrs. Jo. and Cary Ellis Stern, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - La Reclama Cuban Factory, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Latham, Ernest D., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Latson, Tamblyn and Pickard, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lawry, Mrs. Julia E., 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lawson, James S., Esq., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lawyers Title Insurance and Trust Co., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Leavitt, George W., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Leavitt, Mrs. H.H., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Leavitt, Rev. H.H., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Leavitt, Mary A., M.D., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - LeCount, Mr. and Mrs. George H., Jr., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lee, Mrs. Charlotte R., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - LeFevre, George A., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Lehrenkrauss and Sons, 1911-1912 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Lehrenkrauss, J. and Sons, 1913-194 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Leonard, Mrs. A.E., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Lesser, H. and J.J., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Levick, Edwin, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Levy, Aaron, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Lewis, Jerome C., Esq., 1911-1912 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Lewis, Nelson P., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Lillie, Miss Mary S., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Lincoln Safe Deposit Co., 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Linton, John F., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Linton, Mrs. Rebecca C., 1912-1914 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Littlefield, Rev. M.S., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Livingston, Robert, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Loeser, Frederick and Co., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Lord, Arthur, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Lord, Arthur, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Lovelace, Miss Mary E., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Lowerre, Mrs. Lulu J., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Lutringer, Mrs. Emilie, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - General L Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - General L Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - General L Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - General L Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - General L Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Maas, Edward, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - MacDonald, Robert M., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - MacDougall, E.A., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Mackintosh, Mrs. M.E., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Maddox, P.W., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Magnusson, Miss Louise, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Mahoney, James, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Main, William A., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Malarkey, John J., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Malone, Mrs, Annie, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Maltbie, Milo R., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Maltbie, Milo R., Esq., 1911-1921 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Maltine Company, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Manchester Trust Co., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Manor Realty Co., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Manor Realty Co., 1919-1921 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Martens, William F., 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Martin, Thomas F. Realty Co., 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Massachusetts Chocolate Co., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Matteson, Rev. William B., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Maynard, Edwin P., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - McAdoo, Hon. William G., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - McAneny, Hon. George, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - McCarroll, Hon. William, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - McCormick, Mrs. Mary G., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Mcgahie, William J., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - McGoldrick, Edward J., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - McKay, John S., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - McKinney, Miss Mya, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - McLaughlin, Alonzo G., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - McMillan, Emerson, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Meagher, John J., Esq., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Mear, Mrs. Catherine F., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Mear, Thomas J., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Mechanics Bank, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Menken Bros., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Mercantile Trust and Deposit Co. of Baltimore, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Merchants Credit Adjustment Co., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Merchants Exchange National Bank, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Merklee, Frank C., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Merriam, Rev. G., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Metz, Hon. H.A., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Metz, Morris, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Michel, David, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Miller, Hon. Cirus C., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Mitchel, Hon. John P., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Modlinski, Stanislaus, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Montgomery, Robert A., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Moore, F.A., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Moore, W.H. Subscription Agency, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Morey, James S., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Morrow, Tobert H., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Morse, Ernest C., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Morese, George F., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Mueller, Geo. Realty Co., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Munger, Charles A., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Munger, Mrs. Harriet C., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Munger, H.C., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Munger, H.T., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Munson, Frank C., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Murphy, Frank K., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Murray, Charles O., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Myers and Goldsmith, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Myles Construction Company, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - General M Correspondence, 1983-1915 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - General M Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - General M Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - General M Correspondence, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - General M Correspondence, 1919-1920 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - General M Correspondence, 1928-1938 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Neill, George, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Nelson, James W., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Nelson, Z.O. and Son, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - New York Telephone Company, 193-1915 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - New York Times, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Nichols, C.M., 1919-1921 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Norgren, Eric, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Norris, Mrs. Wilhelmina, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - General N Correspondence, 1911-1915 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - General N Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - General N Correspondence, 1917-1937 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Oatka Mining Co., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - O'Brien, M.C., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - O'Connells Bay Ridge Express, 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - O'Keefe, Hon. Arthur J., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Ordway, Edward W., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Ornamental Lighting Pole Co., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Orne, J.D., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Osborne, Hon. Thomas M., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Otis Elevator Co., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Outlook Company, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - General O Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Pach, Lester, Esq., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Palmer and Serles, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Pastre's Automobile Garage, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Patterson, H.S., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Patterson, Mortimer B., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Peabody, Miss Susan P., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Peacock, R.J., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Pack, George L., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Perry, Robert C., Esq, 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Phelan, F.V., 1914 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Philadelphia Association of Credit Men, 1914-1915 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Pickens, Cox and Condor, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 155)